myholidays.com 2018-08-22

# myholidays-PrivacyPolicy

## Privacy Policy

####  Privacy Policy and Cookies

At myholidays.com (MH) we respect your need to understand how your personal information is dealt with. We have set out this Privacy Policy to familiarize you with our practices and demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. We may change the content of this website at any time whenever it deems appropriate and necessary in our opinion without prior notice and consequently our privacy policy may change at any time in the future. You agree to revisit the privacy policy page regularly and your continued access to or use of the website will mean that you agree to the changes.

####  Personal Information

Personal information means data that can be used to identify any individual such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, e - mail address, credit card number, cardholder name, expiration date, information about the travel, bookings and all details that may be requested while any customers visits or uses the website.

When you browse through the website, we may collect information regarding the domain and host from which you access the Internet for operational and security purposes, the Internet Protocol address of the computer or Internet Service Provider you are using, and anonymous website statistical data. The Website uses cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Personal Information will not be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. We use first party cookie and third party cookie for better targeting and tracking purpose. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

You may be asked for certain personal information anytime you are in contact with MH directly or indirectly through a third party. We will get any kind of personal information if you choose to give it to us in following circumstance: 

  * When you make a reservation or purchase any travel related products from our website or through our customer service team - by email, letter, fax, on the phone or in physical store;
  * When you register with us, , subscribe to our newsletter, enter competitions / contest, send us queries or register for promotions;
  * when you take part in surveys or provide us with feedback
  * When you engage with us in any online or offline event, promotions, page hosted by us on a third party platform or location
  * When you engage with our affiliate partners, agents , channel sales /service partners, suppliers

The personal information collected is primarily used to pass on to third party suppliers where it is necessary to process your travel product related booking, enquiry or participation. Your details may be passed to countries outside of the State of Qatar in order to process and arrange for the products and services you request or confirm your participation. These details may also pass through our online frauds detector service partner to identify potential threats. When you submit your booking or request to us and/or participate in our initiatives, you agree that you authorize myholidays. Com to use and transfer your personal information in this manner.

The personal information we collect helps us to keep you posted about MH’ latest product announcements, offers, promotions and events. It also allows us to improve our services, content and advertising. We may also use the personal information to improve our product offering, develop, and deliver products, services, content and advertising.

We may use personal information to send you important notices and communications regarding our products and services availed or changes to the terms and conditions and policies. Personal information may also be used internally for research, analysis and auditing.

####  Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. This feature of web browser software that allows web servers to temporarily store information within your browser, which in turn allows us to recognize the computer used to access MH website. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control and delete how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. You can also edit your browser options to choose not to receive cookies in future. Cookies do not store any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., name, address, etc.).

Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our website. MH uses cookies to personalize your experience on the website, and with respect to advertisements. We may also use such cookies to display an advertisement to you while you are on the website or to send you an email focusing on destinations in which we think you might be interested. None of this information is passed to any third party, and is used solely by us to provide you with a better user experience on the website.

MH and its partners may use cookies or other technologies to track and record anonymous, non personal information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to measure advertising effectiveness. We may also collect non personal information about your visit to our website, based on your browsing (click stream) activities. This information may include the pages browsed and products and services viewed or booked. We may also use this information to measure the usage of advertising banners, other click through from the website.

A cookie may also be placed by our server. Such cookies are used only for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our website and no personal information is gathered from you by the use of these cookies, nor is this information shared with any third parties. Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third - party advertising companies or advertisement providers or servers. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about travel - related goods and services that you may be interested in or any goods and services of potential interest to you. The information they collect does not include your personal information.

The third - party advertising companies or advertisement providers may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of ads. Any such information is anonymous. They may use this anonymous information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information is anonymous, and does not link online actions to an identifiable person.
